



BACKGROUND

My name is Pedro Guerra and i live in Portugal. I design and develop new media content.

My main goal in creative projects is the detail of animations and pixel perfect interfaces, using video, sound, svg graphics, gifs or animated sprites to create the all experience.

Working along 12 years in the creative industries, i worked for several companies such as Mega, Triworks and R3born designing and developing multimedia products.

WEBSITE

http://www.petewar.com

EXPERIENCE

Interface Designer at Pete War

October 2015 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Web/UI Design, Graphic Design, Branding, Video and Sound Design.

UI Designer & Developer at Mega - The Privacy Company

October 2014 - August 2015 (11 months)

Design Interface Interactions for Mobile. Focus on Android Lollipop theme and IOS.

UI Designer at R3born Interactive

March 2013 - January 2014 (11 months)

Focus on UI and UX design and Digital Illustration.

Interactive Designer at **Triworks**

April 2009 - March 2013 (4 years)

Actionscript 2 and 3 (Flash) programmer. UI and UX designer.

Interactive Designer at DREAMLAB digital story makers

January 2009 - April 2009 (4 months)

Actionscript 2 and 3 (Flash) programmer.

Interactive Developer / Graphic Designer at Freelancer

January 2008 - January 2009 (1 year 1 month)

Focus on Interface Web Development and UI Design.

Interactive Developer at **Triworks**

January 2004 - January 2008 (4 years 1 month)

Web Development and Designer.





PROJECTS

Mega

Interface design for IOS and Android.

Sketch, Invision, Illustrator, Flash, Photoshop, Premier, After Effects

MegaBox

Steaming online music platform created by Kimdotcom.

Fireworks, Photoshop, Flash, Illustrator, prototype wireframes

OXA - OffRoad Xplorer

Design and develop web interface and develop mobile widgets.

Sketch, Invision, Photoshop, Actionscript 3.0, Premier

Bwcolors

When black meets white. Rock and Electronic music tunes.

Logic Pro, Ableton Live, Guitar and Bass, Synthethizers

Peninsular Port Services

Design and develop the website interface.

Html5, Canvas, Javascript, CreateJs, Sketch, Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash

Gourmet Lovers

Re-Branding graphic content.

Photoshop, Illustrator

HONORS AND AWARDS

The Fwa - Soty (Favourite website of the day)

Website of the day for **Triworks.net 2007**

The Fwa - Soty (Favourite website of the day)

Website of the day for Triworks.net 2008.

PUBLICATIONS

Design Icons

Tashen 2009

Showcase of best websites in the world.





SKILLS

Graphic Design Digital Media Digital Illustration ActionScript Sound Design **Adobe Creative Suite Vector Illustration** Programming UIX **Work Simplification Sound Editing** Logic Pro JavaScript Canvas JavaScript Libraries **Ableton Live** User Interface Design

EDUCATION

Universidade de Aveiro

Economics

Universidade da Beira Interior

Business Administration and Management, General

LANGUAGES

English and Portuguese (native)

INTERESTS

Sound Design, Bodyboard, Technology, Photographic, Video

INDEPENDENT COURSEWORK

IEFP - Formador CAP

Adobe Flash Certification